This is JobsAgr — an autonomous job discovery agent
built on the ElizaOS framework.
Spinning up the local agent instance.
LLM runs on Nosana GPU cloud — no OpenAI dependency.
This is the chat interface.
I'm giving it x.com/solana as the first target.
The agent triggers its custom SCRAPE_X_PROFILE action —
profile → website → careers page → jobs.
Job board is empty right now.
Queuing x.com/arbitrum and x.com/layerzero_core.
Each target runs its own pipeline concurrently.
Watch the dashboard — listings are starting to appear.
Actions completing in real-time.
LayerZero finished first — clicking a listing to verify.
Live job posting page — pulled and stored
entirely by the agent. No manual searching.
Terminal confirms — Arbitrum's job links
fetched and being processed.
Dashboard — Solana, Arbitrum, LayerZero.
All three discovered and listed automatically.
Targets are entered manually for now —
but full autonomy is the next step.
A self-updating feed, any industry, any niche.
Powered by AI.